Scopus right what's hayver it's I've
written it's the best let's break all
right details break oh yes well actually
it would you like employee motive enough
right actually some people make you code
on the whiteboard we tried this early on
and it didn't work at all
um it just like stress people out who
are probably good that guy be stressed
out if someone asked me to color on a
whiteboard
um so now we just ask like simple
questions and they're like stuff that
like if you are actually like familiar
with the fields you will just know off
the top of your head and if you're not
then you won't like simple machine
learning questions and the question that
I'm really trying to ask without asking
is have you ever actually done any of
this stuff or do you just talk about it
do you like a guru oh yeah you started
bad there just eat one two one two three
[Music]
Thanks I heard I want a bottle ass
that's what I heard I want
what is your favorite careful time
pay attention Alexis
he's gonna
yeah yeah was it so late in the race
while we choose late if you'd like
yeah our first Lexus um this thing looks
like I feel like I actually am in a boat
right now you can do stop it go which is
really nice
does the cat except on Jewish power yes
it doesn't same thing as they did
previously
okay it's cuz it's a hybrid yes but
actually it because it has the
sweetheart
someone else on open power was
complaining about the wind okay said the
wind is the wind is terrible like that
was the biggest problem on the road trip
yeah well which power which cars on the
red floor I mean thought you went onto
the floor oh the other guy is are
severed are you saying yeah like when
the wind would cut out when he died like
something that breaks the wind it just
would not adapt quickly at all down more
down on the road
I mean yeah yeah we know
he was late yeah that he was late before
it didn't feel like it went hard on the
brakes very didn't like why now for
something Oh on the brake
yeah no before before before yes well so
what's gonna go with the wind so
partially is like for this to you Arthur
sir we have been different like integral
gains so it is gonna adapt the less fast
and on the Honda I think it's more the
angle offset line right because that's
kind of how wind shows up yes what he
does genetic it's like a windows offset
how about the people punking insurance
so well ping-pong is mainly like a
problem for the Prius yeah if the Prius
is significantly worse than the other
cars yeah this is a quiet relaxed copula
guys I stayed up really late last night
you know what I got you know I got done
last night and decrypted the rav4 for a
black so I have all the Toyota
encryption figured out we're going to
we're going to really stop let me go
release a PCM reflash that will let you
two have your rav4 do full stop and go
but no no that it's just the CPB thing
to be honest we should have bought the
hybrid cars the time yeah you know I
feel very accomplished I'm a man as a
whole it's a whole mess to notice stuff
but it's all pwned now I'm very sad that
there's no read command though yeah I
mean just an exploit but won't let you
read there's no good way to just read
ECU's without like opening him up or
something I thought I had something
clever last night it doesn't work no
don't have to press the button oh yeah
it's just not coming up because of the
born it's about one other thing yeah
will you buy a pesticide this I buy it
why would I buy a tests I haven't tested
it's right here yeah which do you think
I am guys or I'm gonna buy something
call it castle like way moe
so the yeah there was a question before
what is so oil about the Prius and if it
is different Arbor yeah we believe it's
different like the PC particular is like
a different steering module than all the
other cars or at least when it comes
down to controlling it
I mean Prius is the only one that can do
can do parking yes what is the cable on
the left for power oh this is this is
the comma power yeah it's nowhere near
as nice as the color Powers we're gonna
sell constantly power that the JIRA
so that's actually a facility to pause
right now on the shop you can buy your
very own variant of that the one that
we're selling is even nicer than the one
we're using right now combo power it's
$20
[Music]
Oh compile it's not gonna pull over for
emergency vehicles quite yeah guys beats
Rock
you know I'm always a fan of the fire
trucks go got somewhere to be
there's a big fire in our town
now what the cruise control we actually
like we can't command going 42 even when
it says 28 or something
I don't think so now it's well if we
send the 28 we can't have the deluxe or
anything above 20 yeah they're gonna
block it but can we send 42 well that's
the thing that means a try so we might
need to try to send like 42 even if they
if they see us I mean this is another
thing we can fix with a PC I'm on I have
we're gonna have this all fixed on the
rav4 yeah it's actually uh so it's
encrypted but I I didn't even have to
read it they released a firmware update
for it on December 21st so I just got to
use the
can so there was a question can they
find out that I play white I call la
fronte 2009 well the answer is no that's
the band question okay you know what by
a panda and do it bro I believe in you
passenger side what's her name Academy
so this is my monitor air go away let me
plug back in the stuff oh nice I'm
losing this deal Jeff yes you look that
you're afraid we're gonna giraffe is
Lexus compatible so this is the most
popular Lexus this is a lexus RX to make
sure that it's decent we were talking on
the way out here this thing is like half
the torque of the Corolla yeah
not because the actual torque is any
different because this thing is a boat
why she fell off the gear on dude I'm
not even touching that we didn't try to
block it in Iran but if you put effort
into trying to unblock I don't know man
I'm not touching that yeah I think I
think we don't do anything to vlog it I
don't know if it's your government of
our government or somebodies government
you know you guys all know out there
that I'm not about pissing governments I
know I'm friends with government spends
a lot of time I respect their authority
and in fact mr. limited you're setting
limiter can limited just refer to know
it could in this case use coupling it
like we do use in our own limit for my
Creator so how fast we can come into
work but as far as Mac star who use all
the thought that the care allows us to
use
which is your feet of love microphone
weakness what do you wanna know about it
it's right it's very popular a lot of
people seem to really like it
you guys know we have a problem with
stopped car fusion if you're using open
pilot you know be really careful when
you're coming up on a red light going
faster than like 45 35 we might need to
do the war before we really I have to
press the button twice if I resume it
from once but if you start sighs I
should stop but then you have to burst
again it did that a Presta to engage and
okay well this is another reason we're
having peace of yams bros super
splashing of a violent yes we do
you recognize camp a vision can you not
check whether I'm combined to save other
Misty's
yeah we do the rather help are oblivious
anything
the problem is that the other has a lot
of false positives so we need cover
confirmation to to recognize a stop the
vehicles that I never feel that I never
seen moving before
my spell bees again
whether say
oh they will turn the scobie's off we'll
brainstorm about win my stuff
Kofi's thanks for joining this is the
first lexus RX mopeds the first lexus
was very much definite from the Toyota
oh I mean that was flight code changes
yeah we'll just change our porting guide
to be the Toyota and Lexus ported guide
you know we're kind of weird really hard
getting out getting a great guide
together so you can port your
unsupported Toyota this is good so you
can get your unsupported Toyota or Lexus
working with open pilot so by your Aeons
let's go